Search Menu

English |  Bahasa Indonesia

Close

* [ ] 
    
    Online

* [ ] 
    
    Delivery

* [ ] 
    
    Return & Exchange

* [ ] 
    
    UNIQLO App / Newsletter / StyleHint

* [ ] 
    
    Store

* [ ] 
    
    Products

* [ ] 
    
    Campaign / Coupon / Services

* [ ] 
    
    Legal & Privacy

* [ ] 
    
    Corporate Information

To check the status order, click ‘Track My Order’ and enter the receipt number that you have received via order notification email (Check your email spam if you didn't receive it in your inbox).

There is no receipt number for Click & Collect order. However, you can check it via order notification email or on the UNIQLO App. Click ‘’How to check Click & Collect order‘’ to find out the status order until it arrives at the store (Check your email spam if you don't receive it in your inbox).

Refund will be proceed if the product is returned to the warehouse. Click "MAKE REFUND" button to see the procedures.

Product exchanges can only be made in-store. click the "MAKE EXCHANGE AT STORE" button to see the procedures.

English | Bahasa Indonesia

1. [Uniqlo TOP](https://www.uniqlo.com/uk/en/home)
2. Uniqlo Customer Service

How can we help?
================

1. [UNIQLO](https://www.uniqlo.com/id/en/)
2. [UNIQLO Indonesia Customer Service](https://faq-id.uniqlo.com/?l=en_US)
3. [Legal & Privacy](#)
4. [Privacy Policy](#)

* [ ] 
    
    Online

* [ ] 
    
    Delivery

* [ ] 
    
    Return & Exchange

* [ ] 
    
    UNIQLO App / Newsletter / StyleHint

* [ ] 
    
    Store

* [ ] 
    
    Products

* [ ] 
    
    Campaign / Coupon / Services

* [ ] 
    
    Legal & Privacy

* [ ] 
    
    Corporate Information

Q. Privacy Policy
-----------------

**1\. Website Privacy Policy**

This Website Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to the UNIQLO website ("Website"). We value Our customers' privacy and appreciate Your trust that We will respect Your privacy in a careful and sensible manner. By visiting the Website and/or using the products and services made available to You on the Website, You are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please read this policy carefully.  
Our business is constantly evolving and Our Privacy Policy and the Website Terms of Use will change from time to time. We may e-mail periodic reminders of Our notices and terms of business, unless You have instructed Us not to, but You should check Our Website frequently to see the current changes. Unless stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy applies to all information that We have about You and Your account.  
If You use Our Website continuously and/or use the products and services that We provide to You, then You have agreed to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  
We will not sell Your information to anyone. We are part of the parent company and We will share information with Our parent company and affiliates.  
If You choose to visit the Website, Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and Our Website 

**2\. Customer Information Collected**

Below are the types of information We gather:  
  
**"Automatic Information"**  
We hope You are aware that Our Website has servers that automatically recognize information about Your visit which will help improve the quality of Our services. We may collect information, even if You do not register with Us. We collect and process information which identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person or device to whom that information pertains (“**Personal Information**”):  
"**Customer Personal Data**" (including users of software applications), namely data consisting of:

*  Name, age, gender, email, telephone number, date of birth, address, city, province, zip code, product selection, password, bank account and credit-card details and/or any other data required by Us with respect to the use of Website  

* Information that You provide when You enter a competition/contest or promotion that We sponsor or when You report a problem on Our Website;  

* Your correspondence to Us when You contact Us at [here](https://faq-id.uniqlo.com/contactus/) 

**“Personal Data of Job Applicants”**  
Contact and/or provide information to Job Applicants, and/or for other important uses in recruitment activities.  
Information about You when You use the internet (e.g. Your home URL, IP address and Top Level Domain), Your browser type, country and telephone area code of Your computer location, the pages of Our Website that You visit, the advertisements You click on, and all searches items on Our Website (“**User Information”**). Statistical data about users browsing and user patterns and does not identify individual users. We will also collect personal data from third parties who have received Your consent to submit this information to Us.  
**Mobile Application (if applicable)**  
When You download or use an application provided by UNIQLO or its affiliates and, where applicable, have requested or requested Your consent regarding the location function, We will receive information about Your location from Your mobile application device, including a unique identifier contained in Your device.  We will use this information to provide location-based services, such as search results, and personalized content. Most of the mobile device applications have a function to turn off the location function.  
**Marketing (if applicable) and Newsletter**

* Please note that We will send detail products or services that We offer to You based on information that We identify as products or services of interest to You. If You indicate preferences when providing Personal Information to Us, We will use Your preferences to determine what information We will provide to You.
    
* If You do not want Your preference to receive this information from Us or wish to change the media communication (via e-mail or post) We use to contact You, please contact Us in writing using the contact details stated below.
    
* Please note that by registering Your e-mail on Our site, You will be automatically registered to the e-newsletter on Our system and We may send You personalize greeting, information or communication through our media such as mobile application by APP push, e-mail notification and other channel We might develop in future, based on Your Personal Data, past purchase and store that You have visited in the past.
    
* By agreeing to Our terms and conditions (please choose and pay close attention): participating in competitions/contests held by Us or on Our behalf, or joining Our membership, You have agreed that We will use Your Personal Information. We will not know or be unable to find out about the collection of Personal Information that is not supervised by parents or under the age of 18. If You are under 18 years of age, You are not expected to use this Website or submit Your Personal Information to Us unless You have received consent from, and have received supervision from, Your parent or guardian. You represent and warrant that You are at least 18 (eighteen) years old or are married and are not under guardianship or custody and that You are legally capable and have the right to bind yourself to this Privacy Policy. If You do not meet those conditions but still access or use the Website, You represent and warrant that Your act of signing up, accessing or conducting other activities within the Application have been approved by Your parents, guardians or custodian. You expressly waive any rights under the applicable laws to cancel or revoke any and all consents You provided according to this Privacy Policy when You are deemed legally mature.

**Information You provide**

We collect aggregate information about customer access or visits to the Website and information provided by customers, such as when You registered and communicated with Us electronically.

**Registration**

You agree that:

* The Personal Data that You provide to Us as a customer is true, accurate, current and up to date in all aspects.
    
* You will notify Us of changes to Your Personal Data by contacting Us at [here](https://faq-id.uniqlo.com/contactus/)
    
* You agree not to impersonate an individual or company or use a false name or a name that You are not entitled to use
    
* You must keep Your registration information secure and not disclosed to other third parties.

**3\. Use and Disclosure of Customer Information**

We treat Personal Information as confidential information and Information about Our customers is an important part of Our business. We share customer information only on a limited basis and with Our parent companies and affiliates, Our business partners, Our suppliers We engage to process data on Our behalf, government authorities, successors who have the right to do Our business. We share this information on a limited basis with the agents We have used in the past to send letters and e-mails, reduce repetitive information from customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, and provide customer service. Given that in reality the internet is a global environment, We collect and process personal information by involving international transmissions.  
The data We collect will be transferred and stored in locations outside the jurisdiction of Indonesia, however, such data will always be stored in a safe condition and in accordance with applicable regulations. The data will also be processed by third parties as suppliers that We involve to process the data. By submitting Your personal data, You agree to the transfer, storage or processing of data. We will take all necessary steps to ensure that Your data is stored securely under this privacy policy.  
We use the Customer Personal Data provided to Us by individuals for only the following purposes: 

* to communicate with You;
    
* to maintain and improve customer relationship;
    
* to assess, process and provide products, services and/or facilities to you;
    
* to administer and process any payments related to products, services and/or facilities requested by You;
    
* to establish Your identity and background;
    
* to respond to Your enquiries or complaints and resolve any issues and disputes which may arise in connection with any dealings with Us;
    
* to provide You with information and/or updates on Our products, services, upcoming promotions offered by Us and/or events organized by Us and selected third parties which may be of interest to You from time to time;
    
* for direct marketing purposes via SMS, phone call, email, fax, mail, social media and/or any other appropriate communication channels to members of Our loyalty program in accordance with their consent;
    
* to facilitate Your participation in, and Our administration of, any events including contests, promotions or campaigns;
    
* to maintain and update internal record keeping;
    
* for internal administrative purposes;
    
* to send You seasonal greetings messages from time to time;
    
* to send You invitation to join Our events and promotions and product launch events;
    
* to monitor, review and improve Our events and promotions, products and/or services;
    
* to process any payments related to Your commercial transactions with Us;
    
* to process and analyse Your Personal Data either individually or collectively with other individuals;
    
* to conduct market research or surveys, internal marketing analysis, customer profiling activities, analysis of customer patterns and choices, planning and statistical and trend analysis in relation to Our products and/or services;
    
* to share any of Your Personal Data with the auditor for Our internal audit and reporting purposes;
    
* to share any of Your Personal Data pursuant to any agreement or document which You have duly entered with Us for purposes of seeking legal and/or financial advice and/or for purposes of commencing legal action;
    
* to share any of Your Personal Data with Our joint venture/business partners to jointly develop products and/or services or launch marketing campaigns;
    
* to share any of Your Personal Data with insurance companies necessary for the purpose of applying and obtaining insurance claims, if necessary;
    
* for audit, risk management and security purposes;
    
* for detecting, investigating and preventing fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities;
    
* for enabling Us to perform Our obligations and enforce Our rights under any agreements or documents that We are a party to;
    
* to transfer or assign Our rights, interests and obligations under any agreements entered into with Us;
    
* for meeting any applicable legal or regulatory requirements and making disclosure under the requirements of any applicable law, regulation, direction, court order, by-law, guideline, circular or code applicable to Us;
    
* to enforce or defend Our rights and Your rights under, and to comply with, Our obligations under the applicable laws, legislation and regulations;
    
* for other purposes required to operate, maintain and better manage Our business and Your relationship with Us, which We notify You of at the time of obtaining Your consent.

We use the Personal Data of Job Applicants provided to Us by individuals for only the following purposes: 

* Contacting and/or providing information to employment applicants, and other uses necessary for employment and recruiting activities.
    
* If Your application is unsuccessful, We will keep Your Personal Data for a reasonable period in accordance with Our internal policies and procedures and for administration and statistical analysis purposes.
    
* If Your application is successful, We will process Your Personal Data for purposes regarding employment with Us, including to communicate with You, manage, improve and maintain effective human resources administration, process Your payroll, respond to Your enquiries or complaints, improve and facilitate employee performance and salary reviews, monitor compliance with Our internal policies and procedures, rules and regulations, handbooks and guidelines, code of conduct, evaluate Your performance, enable Us to plan and monitor training requirements, conduct health checks on You, facilitate Your secondment and transfer within UNIQLO and/or the UNIQLO’s group of companies and other purposes that are necessary or related to Your employment with Us as set out in Our internal employee policies.

In addition, if You provide Your home postal address online, You will receive periodic mails from Us containing information on new collections, new products, new store locations, or promotional offers or upcoming activities. There are times when We also send offers to selected UNIQLO customer groups on behalf

* of other companies. When We do this, We do not give that company Your name and address. If You do not wish to receive such submissions and e-mail address updates, or wish to remove Your name from Our list, please contact Us in writing using the contact details stated below, where such removal will take at least 3 (three) days.
    
* We announce accounts and other personal information in accordance with and when We believe such announcement steps are appropriate to comply with the law, implement or apply Our Website Terms and Conditions and other agreements, or protect the rights, property or security of the Website, Our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set out in this Privacy Policy. If UNIQLO or all of its assets were acquired substantially by one or more third parties as a result of a merger, sale, consolidation, or liquidation, customer information may be one of the assets transferred. We may display the data related to product reviews based on the data You provide when you write a review for the respective product. We may display the provided reviews on Uniqlo websites around the world.

**4\. Links**

Certain activities through the Website, such as special promotions may be linked to those from other unrelated third party companies that offer You the option to share Your personal information with the third party. We will not share Your personal information with those third party companies; only You can if You make that choice.  
Links provided on the Website to third party websites are provided as a convenience to You and We do not control those websites nor their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. Linked websites are responsible for their own privacy policy and You should check those websites for their respective privacy policy. Some third party companies may choose to share their personal data with Us but that sharing is governed by such third party company's privacy policy.

**5\. Security**

Confidentiality of Your Personal Information is of utmost importance to Us. We are committed to offering Our customers a safe and secure environment. Our servers utilize SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology to help protect Your personal information. By using an SSL-compatible browser such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox and Safari, You can help ensure that Your personal identifiable information is unavailable to unauthorized users and processed confidentially.

In the unlikely event that We believe that the security of Your personally identifiable information in Our possession or control may have been compromised, We may notify You at Our absolute discretion. If a notification is appropriate or required by law, We would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances and if We have Your e-mail address, We may notify You by e-mail. By using this Website, You consent to Our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.  
We will use all reasonable efforts to protect and secure Your Personal Information against access, collection, use or disclosure by unauthorized persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage or similar risks. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although We will do our best to protect Your Personal Information, You acknowledge that We cannot guarantee the integrity and accuracy of any Personal Information which You transmit over the Internet, nor guarantee that such Personal Information would not be intercepted, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by unauthorized third parties, due to factors beyond our control.

**6\. Retention of Personal Information**

**a.** Your Personal Information will only be held for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected, or for as long as such retention is required or authorized by applicable law. We shall cease to retain Personal Information, or remove the means by which the Personal Information can be associated with You as an individual, as soon as it is reasonable to assume that the purpose for which that Personal Information was collected is no longer being served by retention of Personal Information and retention is no longer necessary for legal or business purposes.  
**b.** Please note that there is still the possibility that some of Your Personal Information might be retained by the other party,  including by the government institutions in some manner. In the event We share Your Personal Information to the authorized government institutions and/or other institutions that may be appointed by the government authorities or have a cooperation with Us, You agree and acknowledge that the retention of Your Personal Information by the relevant institutions will follow their respective policy on data retention.

**7. Update or Change of Personal Information**

Subject to the applicable law, You may request Us to update and/or to correct Your Personal Information in our possession and control, by contacting Us in writing using the contact details stated below.  
We reserve the right to refuse Your requests to update and/or to correct, some or all of Your Personal Information in our possession or control if permitted or required under any applicable law. This may include circumstances where the Personal Information may contain references to other individuals or where the request for access or request to correct is for reasons which We reasonably consider to be trivial, frivolous or vexatious.

**8. Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may review and amend this Privacy Policy at our sole discretion from time to time, to ensure that it is consistent with our future developments, and/or changes in legal or regulatory requirements. If We decide to amend this Privacy Policy, We will notify You of any such amendments by means of a general notice published on the Website and/or website, or otherwise to Your e-mail address set out in Your account. You agree that it is Your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy regularly for the latest information on our data processing and data protection practices, and that Your continued use of Our Website, communications with Us, or access to and use of the services following any amendments to this Privacy Policy will constitute Your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and all of its amendments. The latest version of the Privacy Policy is always available on our Website. Please review this Privacy Policy every time before you deal with us to be sure you agree with it.

**9\. Acknowledgment and Consent**

**a.** By accepting the Privacy Policy, You acknowledge that You have read and understood this Privacy Policy and You accept all of its terms. In particular, You agree and consent to Us collecting, using, sharing, disclosing, storing, transferring, or otherwise processing Your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
**b.** In circumstances where You provide Us with Personal Information relating to other individuals (such as Personal Information relating to Your spouse, family members, friends, or other parties), You represent and warrant that You have obtained such individual’s consent for, and hereby consent on behalf of such individual to, the collection, use, disclosure and processing of his/her Personal Information by Us.  
**c.** You may withdraw Your consent to any or all collection, use or disclosure of Your Personal Information at any time by giving Us reasonable notice in writing using the contact details stated below, such withdrawal may take at least 3 (three) days.

**10\. Contact Us**

If You have any questions regarding Our Privacy Policy, please contact Us at [here](https://faq-id.uniqlo.com/contactus/)  

 Was this information helpful?

If our FAQs did not answer your question and you need further assistance,  
please contact our customer support team via chat, email or phone.

Please let us know why this article is not helpful.

|     |
| --- |
| The information is hard to understand. |
| This isn’t the information I was looking for. |
| The information displayed does not match the topic or category. |
| I do not agree with policy or procedure on this subject. |
| Others |

Please let us know which part of this page is hard to understand.Please let us know what information you are looking for.Please let us know which parts of the article are not matching.Please let us know your feedback to improve our policy/ service to meet your needs.Please share your reason and how we can improve it.

Note: Please do not fill in any personal information.

Your valued feedback will be shared with our team for review and will be used to help us improve our products and services. We are unable to reply directly to any feedback given here.

Please enter your comments below:

Related FAQs
------------

Related Q&A
-----------

Related Inquiries
-----------------

Related information:
--------------------

Contact UNIQLO Indonesia
------------------------

CHAT SUPPORT

\*Click "CHAT SUPPORT" button to open a window on the page to start chatting with our ChatBot  
\*Please note that IQ Chatbot Support cannot recognize specific information such as order numbers, delivery status, personal information, and product names  
\*In the case our IQ Chatbot Support is unable to answer your inquiry, our Customer Support members will assist you further.  
IQ Chat Support Operating Hours: 9 am - 6 pm(Including weekends and Public Holidays)

\*One of our friendly customer support agents will get back to you via email within 1 business day.  
\*For anything time critical please call us via our customer support phone line.

[Toll Free Phone Number](tel:(001) 80332160290)

Customer Care Operating hours:  
Monday - Sunday: 9am - 6pm  
(Including Public Holidays)

Toll Free Phone Number

(001) 80332160290

Customer Care Operating hours:  
Monday - Sunday: 9am - 6pm  
(Including Public Holidays)

Online Services
---------------

[

Online Shopping Guideline

First time shopping at UNIQLO online? Worry not! You can follow our easy guideline to order your desired product. For first time UNIQLO App downloader, you can also get a Welcome Coupon 25k. Let's get started!](https://www.uniqlo.com/feature/shopping-guide/id/en/)[

Bulk Purchase

Enjoy 10% off and free shipping for order with minimum Rp10,000,000 for team outfit, uniforms, gifts and more!](https://www.uniqlo.com/id/en/spl/bulkpurchase)

[

Product Review

Review our product and get a chance to receive our product samples.](https://www.uniqlo.com/id/en/special-feature/review-sampling)[

Online Alteration Service

You can now alter your favourite pants online, and get them delivered right to your doorstep](https://www.uniqlo.com/id/en/spl/alteration)

COPYRIGHT © UNIQLO CO., LTD. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
